rosetta.com 2019-03-29

# Privacy | Publicis Sapient

This website provides information about Publicis Sapient's general business, software, products, or services. If you have any questions about Publicis Sapient's collection of your data please contact Publicis Sapient at [privacyofficer@publicisgroupe.com](mailto:privacyofficer@publicisgroupe.com).  

## Introduction

Any data collected through the [publicissapient.com](https://publicis.sapient.com/en-us.html) website including Personal Data, will only be used when you register, request information or a response from Publicis Sapient to better target you for further sales and marketing opportunities. Once collected, Personal Data will not be used for a different incompatible purpose without your consent. Sapient Corporation, 40 Water Street, Boston, MA 02109 is regarded as the Data Controller.  

We take the protection of data privacy very seriously. All Personal Data collected through the website application will be treated as strictly confidential and will only be used as set out in this Privacy Notice. The applicable data protection laws shall be respected in full.  

Therefore, please read this Privacy Notice thoroughly. If you disagree with the way Personal Data will be used, please do not use this Website or provide your Personal Data through the Website.  

**I.     Purpose of data collection**

The main purposes of collecting Personal Data through the Website is for marketing and sales reasons. Separately we collect Personal Data for website security and maintenance.  

**II.     What Personal Data do we collect and process?**

Personal Data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (i.e. living individual). 

We collect the following Personal Data through the Website:

  1. Your Personal Information  
We collect the following Personal Data from you: your first and last name, company, title, work email, phone number, country and your reason for contacting us.
  2. Browsing Information:  
We additionally collect limited Personal Data connected with your use of the Website e.g. IP address, browser type, operating system, referring domains and exit links.

**III.     What legal ground(s) do we rely on?**

  1. Where Personal Data is provided by you through the Website, we will obtain your explicit consent. Please note that you can withdraw or revoke your consent to our use of your Personal Data at any time. You always have a choice concerning whether or not you provide Personal Data.  

  2. The use of the Personal Data is further necessary for the purposes of Publicis Sapient's legitimate interest     

    1. in improving our services, so we can better understand your needs and expectations and therefore improve our services to you;
    2. to prevent fraud and to ensure that the use of our web services is complete and without fraudulent behavior;
    3. to ensure the security of our services and to ensure that our offerings are technically secure and functioning properly;

**IV.     With whom do we share Personal Data?**

We will share your Personal Data with employees of Publicis Sapient, including Sales, Marketing, IT and Operations Teams in order to create inter alia email campaigns and other marketing efforts.

We will not disclose your Personal Data to anyone else under any circumstances except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Notice, to successors in title to our business, to establish, exercise or defend our rights, or where required by law.   

**V.     Who is processing the Personal Data?**

Employees of Publicis Sapient (from Sales, Marketing, IT and Operations) are processing your data. Employees of Publicis Sapient Consulting Services are helping with the data storage. Any processing of your Personal Data by these employees is in accordance with our instructions.  Amazon Web Services Ireland Ltd is providing the backup disaster recovery servers which are located in Ireland.

If the services of third parties for the technical maintenance, administration or processing of data are required, the Personal Data will be accessed by these parties only to the extent that is required to ensure a smooth and secure technical handling of the Website and in compliance with applicable law, including with respect to data confidentiality, privacy and security.

**VI.     Viewing, Editing, Updating or Deletion of your Personal Data:**

Please contact [privacyofficer@publicisgroupe.com](mailto:privacyofficer@publicisgroupe.com) if you want to see any Personal Data stored about you in our records. We will honor your legal right to view your Personal Data in accordance with applicable privacy law. If you think that any of the Personal Data collected through the Website is incorrect, confusing or incomplete, please contact [privacyofficer@publicisgroupe.com](mailto:privacyofficer@publicisgroupe.com). You may also ask us to erase, restrict or port your Personal Data and you may tell us if you object to our use of your Personal Data. Personal Data will be stored by us in accordance with our applicable data retention requirements and corporate policies.  

**VII.     Data Security**

We use a variety of methods, such as firewalls, intrusion detection software and manual security procedures, to secure your data against loss or damage and to help protect the accuracy and security of Personal Data and to prevent unauthorized access or improper use. If you think that the Website or any Personal Data is not secure or that there has been unauthorized access to the Website or your Personal Data, please contact [privacyofficer@publicisgroupe.com](mailto:privacyofficer@publicisgroupe.com) immediately.  

**VIII.     Confidentiality**

Please note that we treat Personal Data as strictly confidential.  

**IX.     Data Transfers**

Your Personal Data is transferred to the US which is not considered to have the same level of data protection as in the EU. However, we ensure all data transfers comply with applicable legal requirements. Should you wish to know more about how data is protected or wish to request a copy of the contractual protections please contact [privacyofficer@publicisgroupe.com](mailto:privacyofficer@publicisgroupe.com).  

**X.     Use of cookies or other tracking technology**

A cookie is a small file which is placed on your computer's hard drive. If you choose to accept cookies, the file is added and the cookie helps to analyse web traffic or lets us know when you visit a particular site. Cookies further allow us to respond to you as an individual and we can tailor our operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences when you return to our site and for logged-in users to maintain the session and remember table filters. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not.    

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the Website.  

**XI.     Notification of changes**

Should we wish to change this Privacy Notice, if you have already provided Personal Data through this Website, we will contact you to inform you of the new Privacy Notice and, in some circumstances, we may need to obtain your consent to the changes. In other circumstances, any such changes to this Privacy Notice will be promptly communicated on this page and you should check back to see whether there are any changes. Continued use of the Website after a change in the Privacy Notice indicates your acknowledgement and acceptance of the use of Personal Data in accordance with the amended Privacy Notice.  

If you wish to save this text, please mark the entire statement (e.g. with your mouse) and copy-paste by pushing ctrl-c.

**XII.     Further Information**

For further information on Publicis Sapient please visit our website [https://publicissapient.com](https://publicissapient.com/).  

If you consider that we are not complying with this Privacy Notice or if you have any questions in relation to this Privacy Notice, please contact [privacyofficer@publicisgroupe.com](mailto:privacyofficer@publicisgroupe.com). You may also lodge a formal complaint with your competent data protection authority.  

Updated: 25 May 2018
